

Contacts

Tel: 067 657 42 34

E-mail: maryna.golovina.qa@gmail.com

LinkedIn: marina-golovina-4609961b4

Tech Skills

• English[upper-intermediate+]

Cloud Documents..[strong]

• HTML/CSS.....[basic level]

• Postman.....[basic level]

• SQL....[strong]

Jira, Trello

FigmaDevtools

Fiddler

Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Attention to details
- Problem-solving skills
- Empathy
- Stress management
- Knowledge Sharing and Mentoring

Hobbies

- Travelling
- Yoga
- Self-education
- Literature (philosophical novels, fantasy)

QA

Golovina Marina

I have always been keen on learning new knowledge from different spheres, it creates the unique set of skills and helps in finding substandard decisions. After a few months of learning at QA courses I understand that my passion is testing, because quality is the degree of excellence of everything. I am not afraid of challenges, which stimulate getting new experience and involve the maximum of my potential . I would be happy to become a part of your company, bring mutual benefits, stay up-to-date, improve my skills and become an expert in QA

Courses

| 1. | https://www.begatoday.com[QA 2022] |
|----|---|
| 2. | https://training.epam.com |
| 3. | https://yappi.com.ua |
| 4. | https://yappi.com.ua[Business English upper-intermediate] |

Projects

Testing 2 feasible projects within the confines of studing on BeQA courses: https://dust.foundation

May 2022 — nowadays

- Testing fundamentals
- Requirement Analisys
- Decomposition
- Test Design Techniques
- Test Levels
- Test Case Development
- Cross-platform and Cross-browser Testing
- Localization Testing
- Regression Testing
- Test Result Analisys and Reporting
- Teamwork based on SCRUM methodology

Work Experience

Foreign-Economic Activity Expert in <u>LLC"Trade Support Group</u> of <u>Ukraine"</u>

May 2015 — nowadays Kyiv

- Interaction with suppliers
- Interaction with brokers, customs authorities and UCCI (Ukrainian Chamber of Commerce and Industry)
- Cooperation with transport companies (carriers)
- Working with clients

Senior Economist in JSC"Nadra Bank"

November 2013 — April 2015 Kyiv

- Providing a full range of banking services for legal entities and individuals.
- Preparing reports and present results

Education

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Master of FEA (foreign economic activity)

September 2008 - February 2014